19th-20th Century North American Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 15)
    - Minneapolis, MN (Box 71)
      - Government Buildings (Box 71)
      - Hotels (Box 71)
      - Houses (Box 71)
        - Owre House (Box 71)
        - Wakefield House (Box 71)
        - Willey House (Box 71)
      - Libraries (Box 71)
      - Museums (Box 71)
      - Towers (Box 71)
      - Schools (Box 71)
    - Moltawk, NY (Box 71)
    - Montclair, NJ (Box 71)
      - Churches (Box 71)
        - Central Presbyterian (Box 71)
        - S. Peter Claver Mission (Box 71)
      - Houses (Box 72)
        - Livermore House (Box 72)
    - Montecito, CA (Box 72)
      - Houses (Box 72)
        - Tremaine House (Box 72)
    - Monterey, CA (Box 72)
    - Monterey County, CA (Box 72)
    - Montibello, MD (Box 72)
    - Montpelier, VT (Box 72)
    - Morenci, AZ (Box 72)
    - Morristown, NJ (Box 72)
    - Moundville, AL (Box 72)
    - Mount Carmel, ME (Box 72)
    - Montrose, NJ (Box 72)
    - Mount Desert, ME (Box 72)
    - Mount Diablo, CA (Box 72)
    - Mount Kisco, NY (Box 72)
    - Moylan-Rose Valley, PA (Box 72)
    - Murray Hill, NJ (Box 72)
    - Muskegon, MI (Box 72)
    - Nantucket, MA (Box 72)
    - Napa Valley, C (Box 73)
    - Narragansett Pier, RI (Box 73)
      - Houses (Box 73)
      - Recreation (Box 73)
        - Casino (Box 73)
    - Nashville, TN (Box 73)
      - Churches (Box 73)
        - First Presbyterian Church (Box 73)
      - Exposition (Box 73)
      - Government Buildings (Box 73)
        - State Capitol (Box 73)
      - Houses (Box 73)
        - Belle Meade (Box 73)
        - Belmont (Box 73)
        - The Hermitage (Box 73)
      - Schools (Box 73)
    - Natchez, MO (Box 73)
      - Houses (Box 73)
        - Arlington (Box 73)
        - Auburn (Box 73)
        - The Burr (Box 73)
        - Choctaw (Box 73)
        - D'Evereux (Box 73)
        - Dunleith (Box 73)
        - Hope Farm (Box 73)
        - Longwood (Box 73)
        - Melrose (Box 73)
        - Monteigne (Box 73)
        - Rosalie (Box 73)
        - Stanton Hall (Box 73)
    - Naugatuck, CT (Box 73)
    - Nauvoo, IL (Box 73)
    - Navesick Park, NJ (Box 73)
    - Newark, NJ (Box 73)
      - Churches (Box 73)
      - Houses (Box 74)
      - Office Buildings (Box 74)
      - Schools (Box 74)
    - New Bedford, MA (Box 74)
    - Newburgh, NY (Box 74)
    - New Britain, CT (Box 74)
    - New Brunswick, NJ (Box 74)
    - Newbury, MA (Box 74)
    - Newbury Port, MA (Box 74)
    - New Canaan, CT (Box 74)
      - Houses (Box 74)
        - Boissonnas Houses (Box 74)
        - Black House (Box 74)
        - Breuer House (Box 74)
        - Hodgson House (Box 74)
        - Johnson House (Box 74)
          - Glass House (Box 74)
          - Guest House (Box 74)
        - Kniffen House (Box 74)
        - E. Mills House (Box 74)
        - E. Noyes House (Box 74)
        - Wiley House (Box 74)
    - New Castle, DE (Box 75)
      - Various (Box 75)
      - Immanuel Church (Box 75)
      - Kensey Jones House (Box 75)
      - George Reed House (Box 75)
    - New Castle Island, ME (Box 75)
    - New Ebenezer, GA (Box 75)
    - Newfane, VT (Box 75)
    - New Hamburg, NY (Box 75)
    - New Harmony, IN (Box 75)
    - New Hartford, CT (Box 75)
    - New Harrison, OH (Box 75)
    - New Haven, CT (Box 75)
      - General Views (Box 75)
        - Various (Box 75)
        - The Green (Box 75)
        - Streets (Box 75)
        - Wooster Square (Box 75)
        - Maps (Box 75)
          - By Brockett (Box 75)
          - By Doolittle (Box 75)
          - By Wadsworth (Box 76)
        - Planning (Box 76)
          - Various (Box 76)
          - Church ST. Redevelopment (Box 76)
          - Cooperative Market (Box 76)
          - Long-Range Capital Budget (Box 76)
          - Center of City Study, 1941 (Box 76)
          - Oak ST. Connector (Box 76)
          - Sub-Urban Region, 1947 (Box 76)
          - Super Block, 1945 (Box 77)
        - Banks (Box 77)
        - Cemeteries (Box 77)
        - Churches (Box 77)
          - Various (Box 77)
          - Bethel African Methodist Church (Box 77)
          - Center Church (Box 77)
          - Christ Church Parish House (Box 77)
          - Church of the Ascension (Box 77)
          - First Methodist Church (Box 77)
          - Church of the Redeemer (Box 77)
          - Old Christ Church (Box 77)
          - More Chapel (Chapel of St. Thomas) (Box 77)
          - S. John's Episcopal Church (Box 77)
          - Trinity Church (Box 77)
          - United or North Church (Box 77)
        - Garages (Box 77)
        - Government Buildings (Box 77)
          - Various (Box 77)
          - City Hall (Box 77)
          - Court House (Box 78)
          - Police Station (Box 78)
          - Post Office (Box 78)
        - Hospitals (Box 78)
          - Yale New Haven Hospital (formerly Grace New Haven Hospital) (Box 78)
          - S. Francis Orphanace (Box 78)
          - Winchester Memorial Hospital (Box 78)
        - Hotels (Box 78)
        - Houses (Box 78)
          - Various (Box 78)
          - Admiral Berian House (Box 78)
          - Atwater House (Box 78)
          - Basserman House (Box 78)
          - Beers Street House (Box 78)
          - Timothy Bishop House (Box 78)
          - Bradley House (Box 78)
          - Willis Bristol House (Box 78)
          - Bushnell House (Box 79)
          - Dana House (Box 79)
          - Davies-Wallace House (Box 79)
          - Deforest House (Box 79)
          - Dwight House (Box 79)
          - Eaton House (Box 79)
          - Farnam House (Box 79)
          - Fisher House (Box 79)
          - Gabriel House (Box 79)
          - Hadley House (Box 79)
          - Hillhouse House (Box 79)
          - Hubinger House (Box 79)
          - "Ik Marvel" (Donald Grant Mitchell House) (Box 79)
          - Ingersoll House (Box 79)
          - Norton House (Box 79)
          - Octagonal House (Box 80)
          - Old Morris House (Box 80)
          - Perit House (Box 80)
          - Phelps House (Box 80)
          - John Pierpont House (Box 80)
          - Porter House (Box 80)
          - Pritchard House (Box 80)
          - Lawrence Riggs House (Box 80)
          - Silliman House (Box 80)
          - Nathan Smith House (Box 80)
          - Ithiel Town House (Box 80)
          - Towshend (Box 80)
          - Trowbridge House (Box 80)
          - Watrous House (Box 80)
          - Wheeler House (Box 80)
          - E. Whitney House II (Box 80)
          - Wiggin House (Box 80)
          - Winchester House (Box 80)
        - Apartments-Housing (Box 80)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 80)
        - Museums (Box 80)
          - Historical Society (Box 80)
        - Railroad Stations (Box 80–81)
        - Schools (Box 81)
          - Hill House High School (Box 81)
          - Hopkins Grammar School (Box 81)
          - New Haven State Teacher College (Box 81)
          - Roger Sherman School (Box 81)
        - Stores, Markets, Warehouses, etc. (Box 81)
      - Yale (Box 81)
        - General (Box 81)
        - Various (Box 81)
        - Air Views (Box 81)
        - Maps (Box 81)
        - Early Prints, paintings (Box 81)
        - John Russell Pope, plans proposals (Box 81)
        - J.G. Rogers, drawings (Box 81)
        - Alumni Hall (Box 81)
          - I, 1852-1853 (Box 81)
          - II, 1910-1911 (Box 81)
        - Alumni War Memorial (Box 81)
        - Art & Architecture Building (Box 81)
          - Plans & Sections (Box 81)
          - Exterior (Box 81)
          - Interior (Box 81)
        - Art Gallery I-IV (Box 82)
          - I: Trumbull, 1837 (Box 82)
            Xx Street Hall
          - II: 1836-1866 (Box 82)
          - III: 1926-1928 (Box 82)
          - Projects (Box 82)
          - Plans (Box 82)
          - Exterior (Box 82)
          - Interior (Box 82)
            - Branford Rooms (Box 82)
            - East Granby Room (Box 82)
          - IV: 1952-1953 (Box 82)
            - Projects (Box 82)
              - Kahn Project (Box 82)
            - Plans (Box 82)
            - Exterior (Box 82)
            - Interior (Box 83)
              - 1st Floor (Box 83)
              - 2nd Floor (Box 83)
              - 3rd Floor (Box 83)
              - Exhibitions (Box 83)
                - Alumni at Exhibition, 1960 (Box 83)
        - Athletic Group, Yale Bowl (Box 83)
        - Battell Chapel (Box 83)
        - Berkeley College (Box 83)
        - Berkeley Oval (demolished) (Box 83)
        - Bicentennial Building (Box 83)
          Xx Alumni War Memorial Woolsey Hall
        - Bingham Hall (Box 83)
        - Boat House (Box 83)
        - Bowl (Box 83)
          Xx Athletic Group
        - Branford College (Box 83)
        - Byers Hall (Box 83)
        - Calhoun College (Box 83)
        - Chapel (Box 83)
        - Commons, 1818-1819 (Box 83)
        - Computer Lab (Box 83)
        - Connecticut Hall (Box 84)
        - Davenport College (Box 84)
        - Department of University Health (Box 84)
        - Dinning Hall (Box 84)
        - Divinity School (Box 84)
          - I, (old) (Box 84)
          - II, (New) Sterling Divinity Quadrangle 1932 WA (Box 84)
        - Durfee Hall (Box 84)
        - Dwight Hall II, 1886 (Box 84)
          - I, 1842-1846 (Box 84)
          - II, 1886 (Box 84)
        - Farnam Hall (Box 84)
        - First College House (Box 84)
        - Forestry School (Box 84)
          Xx Greeley Memorial Laboratory & New Haven Houses, Othniel Mash House
        - Fraternity Houses & Tombs (Box 84)
        - Gibbs Laboratory (Box 84)
          Xx Saarine's plan for Physics Building (Pierson-Sage Squares), 1952.
          Xx Sloan Physics Building II
        - Graduate's Club (Box 84)
          Xx New Haven, Houses Bushnell House
        - Graduate's Housing (Box 84)
        - Graduate Schools (Box 84)
          Xx Hall of Graduate Studies
        - Greeley Memorial, Lab (Forestry) (Box 84)
        - Gymnasia (Box 84)
          - I, 1860 (Box 84)
          - II, 1892 (Box 84)
          - III, Payne White, 1932 (Box 84)
            - Plans (Box 84)
            - Exterior (Box 84)
            - Interior (Box 84)
        - Hall of Graduate Studies (Box 84)
        - Hammond Hall (Box 84)
        - W.L. Harness Hall (Box 85)
        - Harness Memorial Quadrangle (Box 85)
        - Hendrie Hall (Box 85)
        - Ingalls Rink (Box 85)
        - Jonathan Edwards College, 1932 (Box 85)
        - Kent Hall, Chemistry Lab, (demolished, 1931) (Box 85)
        - Kline Biology Tower (Box 85)
        - Kline Geology Lab (Box 85)
        - Kline Science Center (Box 85)
        - Lawrence Hall, 1885-1886 (Box 85)
        - Libraries (Box 85)
          - Library I: Dwight Chapel (Box 85)
          - Library II: Sterling Memorial (Box 85)
            - Various (Box 85)
            - Exterior (Box 86)
            - Interior (Box 86)
          - Beinecke Rare Book Library (Box 86)
        - Linsley-Chittenden Hall (Box 86)
        - Medical School (Box 86)
          - I, Old Campus (Box 86)
          - II, Sterling Hall of Medicine (Box 86)
        - Morse College (Box 86)
          Xx Stiles & Morse Colleges (filed together)
        - North Sheffield (Box 86)
        - Observatory, 1879 (Box 86)
        - Observatory II, office Building (Box 86)
        - Old Campus (Box 86)
          - I (Box 86)
          - II (Box 86)
        - Osborn Hall (Box 86)
        - Osborne Memorial Laboratories (Box 86)
        - Payne White Gym (Box 86)
        - Peabody Museum (Box 87)
          - I, Old (Box 87)
          - II (Box 87)
        - Phelps Hall & Gateway (Box 87)
        - Physics Building (Box 87)
        - Pierson College (Box 87)
        - President's House (Box 87)
          Xx New Haven, Houses – Farnam House
        - Sheffield Hall (Scientific School) (Box 87)
          - I (Box 87)
          - II (Box 87)
        - Saybrook College (Box 87)
          Xx Harness Memorial Quadragle, Branford College
        - Silliman College (Box 87)
        - Sloane Physics Laboratory (Box 87)
          - I (demolished 1931) (Box 87)
          - II (Box 87)
        - Sterling Divinity Quadrangle (Box 87)
          Xx Divinity School II
        - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory (Box 87)
        - Sterling Hall of Medicine (Box 87)
        - Sterling Law Buildings (Box 87)
        - Stiles & Morse College (Box 87)
        - Strathcona Hall (Box 87)
          Xx Sheffield Hall II
        - Street Hall (Box 87)
          - Exterior (Box 87)
          - Interior (Box 87–88)
          - Interior with Art Classes (Box 88)
        - Theater-Drama School (Box 88)
        - Trumbull College (Box 88)
        - Trumbull Gallery (Box 88)
          Xx Art Gallery I
        - University Halls (Commons) (Box 88)
          Xx Woolsey Hall
        - Vanderbilt Hall (Box 88)
        - Weir Hall Architecture School (Box 88)
        - Welch Hall (Box 88)
        - Winchester Hall (Box 88)
        - Woodbridge Hall (Box 88)
        - Woolsey Hall (Box 88)
          Xx Alumni War Memorial
        - Wright Memorial Hall, 1901 (Box 88)
        - Yale Field (Box 88)
    - New Hope, PA (Box 88)
    - New Iberia, LA (Box 88)
    - Newington, CT (Box 88)
    - New Kensington, PA (Box 88)
      - Aluminum City (Box 88)
    - New London, CT (Box 88)
      - Various (Box 88)
      - Bridges (Box 88)
      - Churches (Box 89)
      - Houses (Box 89)
        - Hempstead House (Box 89)
    - New Market, NH (Box 89)
    - New Orleans, LA (Box 89)
      - Various (Box 89)
      - Government (Box 89)
      - Houses (Box 89)
    - New Paltz, NY (Box 89)
    - Newport, RI (Box 89)
      - Various (Box 89)
        - Brick Market (Box 89)
      - Cemeteries (Box 89)
      - Churches (Box 89)
        - Touri Synagogue (Box 89)
        - Trinity Church (Box 89)
      - Government Buildings (Box 89)
        - Colony House (Box 89)
      - Hotels (Box 89)
      - Houses (Box 89)
        - Various (Box 89–90)
        - F.W. Andrews Howe (Box 90)
        - Belcourt (Belmont House) (Box 90)
        - Isaac Bell House (Box 90)
        - Bishop Berkeley House (Whitehall) (Box 90)
        - Bonniecrest (Box 90)
        - Breakers (Box 90)
        - Chateau-Sur-Mer (Box 90)
        - S. Colman House (Box 90)
        - Duncan House (Box 90)
        - T. Dunn House (Box 90)
        - Edgar House (Box 90)
        - Elmhurst House (Box 90)
        - Fairbourne House (Box 90)
        - Fearing House (Box 90)
        - Gambrill House (Box 90)
        - Robert Goelet House "Southside" (Box 90)
        - J.N. Griswold House (Box 90)
        - The Hypotenuse (Box 90)
        - L.C. Joseph House (Box 90)
        - King House (Box 90)
        - Kingscote (Box 90)
        - P. Lorillard House (Box 90)
        - Malbone (Hall) House (Box 90)
        - Marble House (Box 90)
        - Maquand House (Box 90)
        - Matthews House (Box 90)
        - Miramar (Box 90)
        - Morgan House (Box 91)
        - Ochre Court (Box 91)
        - Oelrich House (Box 91)
        - Rosecliff (Box 91)
        - Sanford House (Box 91)
        - H.A.C. Taylor House (Box 91)
        - Van Buren House (Box 91)
        - Vernon House (Box 91)
        - Watts-Sherman House (Box 91)
        - Wetmore House (Box 91)
          Xx Chateau sur Mer
        - Williams House (Box 91)
      - Libraries (Box 91)
      - Recreation (Box 91)
      - Stores (Box 91)
    - Newport Beach, CA (Box 91)
    - New Rochelle, NY (Box 91)
    - New Salem, OR (Box 91)
    - Newton, MA (Box 91)
    - Newton Centre, MA (Box 91)
    - Newton Lower Falls, MA (Box 91)
    - New York, NY (Box 92)
      - Plans (Box 92)
        - Various (Box 92)
        - 17th Century (Box 92)
        - 18th Century (Box 92)
        - 19th Century (Box 92)
      - Planning (Box 92)
        - Various (Box 92)
        - Harlem Redevelopment (Box 92)
        - Proposed 2 level, streets, sidewalk (Box 92)
      - General Views (Box 92)
        - 17th Century, Nieuw Amsterdam (Box 92)
        - 18th Century (Box 92)
        - 19th Century (Box 92)
        - 20th Century (Box 92)
        - Air views (Box 92)
      - Streets (Box 93)
        - Various (Box 93)
        - Broadway (Box 93)
        - Fifth Avenue (Box 93)
        - Park Avenue (Box 93)
        - Wall Street (Box 93)
      - Airports (Box 93)
        - Idlewild (Kennedy Airport) (Box 93)
          - TWA Terminal (Box 93)
      - Arches (Box 93)
        - Dewey Architecture (Box 93)
        - Washington Architecture (Box 93)
      - Armories (Box 93)
      - Banks (Box 93)
        - Browery Savings Bank (old) (Box 93)
        - Browery Savings Bank (new) (Box 93)
        - Branch Bank of U.S. (Box 93)
        - Chase National Bank (Box 93)
        - Continental Bank (Box 93)
        - Corn Exchange (Box 93)
        - Dry Dock Savings Bank (Box 93)
        - Guaranty Trust Company (Box 93)
        - Irving Trust Co. Building (Box 93)
        - Knickerbocker Trust Co. (Box 93)
        - Manufactures Trust Co. (Box 94)
        - Merchants Exchange (Box 94)
        - National City Bank (Box 94)
        - Second National Bank (Box 94)
        - Stock Exchange (Box 94)
      - Bridges (Box 94)
        - Brooklyn Bridge (Box 94)
        - George Washington Bridge (Box 94)
        - Hall Gate Bridge (Box 94)
        - Henry Hudson Bridge (Box 94)
        - Manhattan Bridge (Box 94)
        - Queensboro Bridge (Box 94)
        - Triborough Bridge (Box 94)
        - Williamsburgh Bridge (Box 94)
      - Churches (Box 94)
        - Various (Box 94)
        - Ascension Church (Box 94)
        - Beth-El Temple (Box 94)
        - B'Nai Jeshurun Temple (Box 94)
        - Broadway Tabernacle (Box 94)
        - Collegiate Reformed (Box 94)
        - Dr's Tyng's Church (Box 94)
        - First Presbyterian Church (Box 94)
        - Grace Church (Box 94)
        - Heavenly Rest Church (Box 94)
        - Holy Communion Church (Box 94)
        - Intercession Chapel (Box 94)
        - Madison Square Presbyterian Church (Box 94)
        - Marble Collegiate (Box 94)
        - Old North Church (Box 94)
        - Park Avenue Methodist Episcopal (Box 94)
        - Puritans Church (Box 94)
        - Riverside Church (Box 95)
        - S. Agnes Chapel (Box 95)
        - S. Bartholomew's (Box 95)
        - S. George's Church (Box 95)
        - S. John's Chapel (Box 95)
        - S. John the Divine, Church of (Box 95)
          - Designs (Box 95)
          - Exterior (Box 95)
          - Interior (Box 95)
        - St. Mark's Church (Box 95)
        - ST. Patrick's Cathedral (Box 95)
        - St. Paul's Chapel (Box 95)
        - St. Peter's (at Citicorp) (Box 95)
          Xx for views of interior see Sculpture – Nevelson, Louise
        - S. Thomas Church (Box 95)
        - S. Vincent Ferrer (Box 95)
        - Temple Emmanuel (Box 95)
        - Trinity Church (Box 95–96)
      - Clubs (Box 96)
        - Century Club (Box 96)
        - Club Royale (Box 96)
        - Colony Club (Box 96)
        - Harvard Club (Box 96)
        - Masonic Hall (Box 96)
        - Metropolitan Club (Box 96)
        - Racquet & Tennis Club (Box 96)
        - University Club (Box 96)
      - Expositions (Box 96)
        - World' Fair 1853 (Box 96)
        - World's Fair 1939 (Box 96)
          - Plans (Box 96)
          - General (Box 96)
          - Foreign Buildings (Box 96)
            - Belgium (Box 96)
            - Brazil (Box 96)
            - France (Box 96)
            - Poland (Box 96)
            - Russia (Box 96)
            - Sweden (Box 96)
          - Industrial Buildings (Box 96)
            - Aviation (Box 96)
            - Budd Mfg. Co. (Box 96)
            - Distillers Building (Box 96)
            - Edison Building (Box 96)
            - Electrical Utilities (Box 96)
            - Ford Building (Box 96)
            - General Motors Building (Box 97)
            - Glass Building (Box 97)
            - Petroleum Industries Building (Box 97)
          - Old Masters Exhibitions (Box 97)
        - Government Buildings (Box 97)
          - Various (Box 97)
          - City Hall (Box 97)
            - Plans, sections & designs (Box 97)
            - Exterior (Box 97)
            - Interior (Box 97)
          - Court Houses (Box 97)
          - Customs Houses (Box 97)
          - Federal Building (Box 97)
          - Municipal Asphalt Plant (Box 97)
          - Municipal Building (Box 98)
          - Post Offices (Box 98)
          - Sub-Treasury Building (Box 98)
          - United National Headquarters (Box 98)
            - Plans, sections & diagrams (Box 98)
            - Exterior (Box 98)
            - Interior (Box 98)
          - United Nations Plaza Center (Box 98)
        - Highways (Box 98)
          Xx Parkways
        - Hospitals (Box 98)
          - Cornell Medical Center (Box 98)
          - Fifth Avenue Hospital (Box 99)
          - Presbyterian Hospital (Box 99)
          - St. Luke's Hospital (Box 99)
        - Hotels (Box 99)
          - Astor Hotel (Box 99)
          - Hotel Pierre (Box 99)
          - Plaza Hotel (Box 99)
          - Ritz-Carlton Hotel (Box 99)
          - Sherry's Hotel (Box 99)
        - Houses – Apartments (Box 99)
          - Various (Box 99)
          - 72nd St. Apts. (Box 99)
          - Ansonia Apartments (Box 99)
          - Beaux-Arts (Box 99)
          - Fifth Ave. Apt-House (Box 99)
          - Glen Oaks Village (Box 99)
          - House of Mansions (Box 99)
          - Manhattan House (Box 99)
          - Rockefeller Apts. (Box 99)
          - Stuyvesant Town (Box 99)
        - Houses-Residences (Box 99)
          - Various (Box 99)
          - 66th St. House (Box 99)
          - Athorpe House (Box 99)
          - Astor House (Box 99)
          - Carnegie House (Box 99)
          - Senator's Clark House (Box 100)
          - Thomas Clark House (Box 100)
          - Collier House (Box 100)
          - Colonnade Row House (Box 100)
          - Davenport House (Box 100)
        - Dekoven House (Box 100)
        - De Peyster Mansion (Box 100)
        - Fairchild House (Box 100)
        - Fiedler House (Box 100)
        - Fonthill House (Box 100)
        - Gerry House (Box 100)
        - Gibson House (Box 100)
        - Gracie Mansion (Box 100)
        - Grammercy Park Houses (Box 100)
        - Guest House (Philip Johnson) (Box 100)
        - Jumel Mansion (Box 100)
        - Kane House (Box 100)
        - Lescaze House (Box 100)
        - Mayer House (Box 100)
        - Morton House (Box 100)
        - Phipps House (Box 100)
        - Pulitzer House (Box 100)
        - Redmont House (Box 100)
      - Reid House (Box 100)
        Xx New York Houses—Henry Villard Residence
      - Rockefeller J.D. House (Box 100)
      - Rollins House (Box 100)
      - Roosevelt House (Box 100)
      - Root House (Box 100)
      - Sanders House (Box 100)
      - Schwab House (Box 100)
      - Senff House (Box 100)
      - Stevens House (Box 100)
      - Stewart House (Box 100)
      - Stone House (Box 100)
      - Taylor House (Box 100)
      - Tiffany House (Box 100)
      - Tredwell House (Box 100)
      - Van Cortland Mansion (Box 100)
      - Vanderbilt House (Box 101)
      - Villard House (Box 101)
      - Wheelock House (Box 101)
      - Stanford White House (Box 101)
      - Whitney House (Box 101)
      - Willow Place (Box 101)
    - Housing (Box 101)
      - Various (Box 101)
      - Abraham Lincoln House (Box 101)
      - Baruch House (Box 101)
      - Fresh Meadows (Box 101)
      - Fresh Meadows (Box 101)
      - Kew Garden Hills (Box 101)
      - Knickerbocker Village (Box 101)
      - Park Chester (Box 101)
      - Queensbridge Houses (Box 101)
      - Suburban Rental Houses (Box 102)
      - Sunnyside (Box 102)
      - Workingmen's Houses (Box 102)
    - Industrial Buildings (Box 102)
    - Libraries (Box 102)
      - Various (Box 102)
      - Astor Library (Box 102)
      - Morgan Library (Box 102)